Do you remember brother?  Last month we all went to
Jodhpur.  What time did you come?
Yes friend, what a great trip it was.  We
enjoyed so much there and also ate the famous food there.
And I liked the dal papad there the best.
Yes, it was really very tasty.
Brother, you reminded me of that place.  I wish I could get that
here too and I also feel like eating dal papad.
Wait, I'll check online now.
Hey friend, I can't see it anywhere online.
Hey brother, what will you be useful for?  You are the
chef of the house.
Okay, should I make it for you?
Face.
Yes, you will make it.  Wait, I will
make Jodhpur for you at home.
Bharat sab jaanu main [Song voice]
Chaudhary
oh it's okay I'm
awake
take it, dal papad is ready for you
Chandni [Music]
[Song voice]
Bhaiya this looks really tasty to me it
feels like I have reached Jodhpur
oh what have you made
this is Jodhpur fame taste you also try it
bhaiya friend what have you made I have
never eaten anything like this in my life